

## IZAM SYUWARI ISHAK

12, Lorong Murni 15, Taman Desa Murni, 13800 Butterworth, Penang

Mobile: +60-125374943 izam.syuwari@moh.gov.my Medical Physicist, Nuclear Medicine Department, Penang Hospital, Ministry of Health

860913-35-5819 (31 years)

# **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Highly motivated, ambitious, team oriented medical physicist with radiation protection skills. 4 years' experience in metrology development management, quality audit for ISO9001 & 14000

### **EDUCATION**



- Bachelor of Science With Honours (Nuclear Science) 2005-2008
  Universiti Kebangsaan Malaysia (UKM)
- Penang Matriculation College 2004-2005
- High School, SMK Datuk Haji Ahmad Said, Penang

### **CAREER SUMMARY**







Nuclear Medicine, Penang Hospital, Ministry of Health 15 Jan 2014 – Now Medical Physicist

Fuji Electric (M) Sdn. Bhd. 29th June 2009 – 15 Jan 2014 Engineer (Sputter Metrology)

Universiti Tenaga Nasional (UNITEN) September 2008 – March 2009 Research Assistant

# TRAINING & COMPETENCIES

<u>Organizers</u>: Ministry of Finance, Khazanah Nasional Berhad & Putrajaya Committee GLC High Performance for Graduate Employability Management Scheme (GEMS) | <u>Date</u>:  $19^{th}$  April  $2009 - 28^{th}$  June 2009

The purpose of the scheme is to enhance the employability of the unemployed graduates. The main objective of the programme is to develop the competencies of the participants based on the industry- driven competency model.

### JOB SCOPE & RESPONSIBILITIES

Company: Nuclear Medicine, MOH | Duration: 15th Jan 2014 - Now | Position: Medical Physicist

- Perform quality control check & testing of biomedical equipment fitness for daily use.
- Manage the preventive maintenance of the equipment and verify its performance.
- Carry out the duties in accordance with the Act 304 (Atomic Energy Licensing Act) and the circular which was gazette in the department.
- Managing and monitoring the radiation protection programme including shielding calculation for radioactive materials safety & security.

Company: Fuji Electric (M) Sdn. Bhd. | Duration: 29th June 2009 – 15th Jan 2014 | Position: Engineer (Sputter Metrology)

- Maintaining overall QC/QA of the equipment & tools for Sputter metrology measurement.
- Introduce new & enhanced current analysis method, improve stability, accuracy, GR&R and reduce measurement time for all machines for time and cost savings.
- Process management designs & manages work processes that are efficient and effective to supports department's goals and objectives.
- Manage and ensure quality compliance of ISO9001:2008 and ISO14000:2004 and as internal auditor.

# INVOLVEMENT AS COMMITTEE/TASKFORCE/PROJECT TEAM

- Annual organization report to National Nuclear Medicine Coordinator Ministry of Health (MOH)
- Committee member of International Conference on Radiation Safety & Security Healthcare Services
  2015
- ICT coordinator for ICT team at Nuclear Medicine Department, Penang Hospital
- Department's statistical cases & cases analysis coordinator
- Protocol Lead for "International Conference On Radiation Safety & Security In Healthcare Services 2017 (ICORSSIHS 2017)"
- Committee member National Nuclear Medicine Conference 2017

### INVOLVEMENT IN QUALITY IMPROVEMENT PROJECTS

- Preparation Process of Tc-99m Radiopharmaceutical In Vertical Laminar Flow Cabinet 2015 (Innovation)
- Improvement Process of Liquid Radioiodine Ablation to Thyroid Patient, Lead Tunnel 2015 (Innovation)

## PRESENTATIONS IN COURSE / SEMINAR / CONFERENCE

- CME Medical Physicist Ministry of Health Malaysia, PICC Putrajaya, Comparison Of Analogue Geiger-Muller and Ionization Chamber for Measuring Exposure Rate In Radioactive Iodin-131
- Radiation Safety Course for Jabatan Kesihatan Negeri P. Pinang Bil2/2015 Ionize & non-ionize radiation
- Radiation Safety Course Bil 2/2016 Nuclear Medicine Department, Penang Hospital
- Radiation Safety Course Bil 1/2017 Nuclear Medicine Department, Penang Hospital
- Role of Medical Physicist in Nuclear Medicine Introduction for Penang Medical Collage's students

### INVOLVEMENT IN RESEARCH

- Comparison of Analogue Geiger Muller and Ionization Chamber for Measuring Exposure Rate in Radioactive Iodine 131 Therapy Patients; by Fatin Nadhirah A.H., Norsuraya A.J., Mohd Hizwan M.Y., Izam Syuwari I., Mohamad Nazreen H.
- Preliminary Results of Determination of The Amount of Fluid to Achieve Faster Radiation Washout In Well Differentiated Thyroid Cancer Patients Undergoing Radioiodine Therapy; A prospective observational study; by Alex K.C.H, Lee Y.F., Fadzilah H., Fatin Nadhirah A.H., Norsuraya A.J., Mohd Hizwan bin M.Y., Izam Syuwari I., Mohamad Nazreen H.
- Surveillance of Lead Tunnel Usage During Preparation And Dispensing Of Radioactive Iodine (I-131) for Thyroid Cancer And Hyperthyroidism Patients In Adherence To The Atomic Energy Licensing Act (Act 304) Standards; by Dr Au MY, Norsuraya A.J, Ahmad Akmal E., Fatin Nadhirah A.H., Izam Syuwari I., Mohamad Nazreen H., Ahmad Lutfi Amir S., Amir Firdaus A.A, Dr. Alex K.C.H., Dr Fadzilah H.

## PROFESSIONAL MEMBERSHIP

- Persatuan Pegawai Sains Fizik Kementerian Kesihatan Malaysia (PERFEKS)
- Institute of Physics Malaysia (MIPM)
- Malaysian Society Of Nuclear Medicine & Molecular Imaging (MSNMMI)

### REFERENCES

Name Mr Mohd Hizwan Mohd Yahya

**Designation** Senior Physicist C52

**Company** Nuclear Medicine Department, Penang Hospital

**Contact No** +60-42225333 ext 2113 (012-5094172)

E-mail: nawhiz@yahoo.co.uk

Name Dr. Fadzilah Hamzah

**Designation** Head of Department, Specialist UD54

**Company** Nuclear Medicine Department, Penang Hospital

Contact No +60-42225333 ext 2117 (017-8067411)

E-mail: drila98hkt@yahoo.com.my